last episode we fixed our energy problem by adding some large Infinity turbines
however we also noticed that we only moved the problem from the batteries to the americium plasma tank
to fix that new issue
we proceeded into increasing our americium plasma production by making a slightly larger fusion reactor
also called compact reactor
here you can see our helper building it
around 100 blocks at a time
now that the reactor can keep up with the turbines
we have a new problem
we are making too much americium plasma
and we can't cool it down fast enough
so we made a mega vacuum freezer
however that was using too much power
so we instead opted for more turbines
next we noticed that our plutonium was getting nuked
so we added more void miners to vegaB
however that made us run out of oganesson
our old setup couldn't keep up with the new usage
so we made a bigger production plant
our old EBFs couldn't handle all the materials required for such plant
so we had to upgrade our cooking station
and that made us fall back to the original problem
which wasn't even a problem before we started making all of these things
before we address again the production issue
we have to fix the transportation one
our old laser could only carry 2 billion EU/t
so we replaced the main line with better ones
which will hold up to 32 billion
and now after all of that working
we notice that our Infinity turbines aren't infinite
and are indeed finishing
anyways after staring at a screen for a lot of time
we have complete our research about what we should be doing next
other than doing twice the same thing just to stage and record it
the result of our efforts is quite simple
we should go on with the main quest line
and so we did some optical circuits
and a new tier of fusion reactor
which we are going to use to make hypogen
the next key material
however there is a catch it requires some nasty stuff
like dragon blood
which we have made a long time ago by slaying the Ender Dragon
while it is crafting
we notice that cooling down that material into a mold takes quite some power
so we have to upgrade our machinery
and you have no idea how many time we have done this process so far
next we realize it takes half an hour to make one ingot of hypogen
due to reasons
we manually cool down the only ingot we have managed to make
so that we can go on with the quests
you can see how the gods are luring us
but we have already finished portal
so we do know that the cake is a lie
we must not fall for it and keep going on
so we proceed into working towards the hypogen coils
but we can't even make infinity ones
while we wait for infinity to build up
we shall check the new power plant a new comrade has been working on
this fuel is then burned inside this reactor to make quite some power
as you can see from these stats
and this is our new total production
anyways
we have managed to make enough coils for the quest
and thus we have unlocked the hypogen Coil one
as the book says
this is quite a weird material
and the new coils made out of it do require a main frame inside each block
however before we get into crafting these
we have to first research them
and thus we run into a new issue
our crypto farm is no longer on par
and we need a better one
so we built a new shed for housing all the new computers
and we start filling them with GPUs and many vents
we even had to order a new batch of GPUs for this operation
it is now time to turn them on
and check if they are properly working
and after some testing and debugging
we found one which didn't receive one GPU
after fixing every issue
we finally managed to start the research of the hypogen coil
with the power of 32,000 terafloops
now that we have unlocked the recipe
we can realize that we can't afford crafting them
we lack some dragon blood
we could make some convoluted process to have some more
but I think we should try a different route
let's try a different quest
like that one
however before making one more of these batteries
we should do something to cut the costs
but before that we need more Infinity catalyst
so let's add some more void miners to the new planets
and while we gather materials
let's do some spring cleaning of our AE2 system
we are going to move the contents of the overfilled cells to some quantum chests
and we should also stock some more unstable dust
with our new machine
we can craft component in a cheaper way
so let's get back to the quests
we now have completed the battery one
the next quest doesn't look too nasty
it's only four blocks that we have to craft
let's see how they are made
it looks manageable
it takes most stuff that we already got
and we can research it
let's get to work
anyways we must first upgrade our power production
so we stepped up our naquadah fuel facility
we now can reach 5 billion EU per tick
our an naquadah line now touches the sky
our machines are working beyond our production
and after mining some more planets
we can finally afford to craft the last piece needed to complete the next quest
a Dimensional Transcendent Plasma Forge
or dtpf for short
and here we go
this multi block is quite big
and for completing the next quest
we needed to have at least Infinity Coils
and thus we have unlocked tesseracts and transcendent metal dust
which can be used for all kind of things
many things have happened since the last time
but let's focus on the most useless ones
we have just noticed that managed to fill one experience obelisk
and it won't let us go over 3,125 levels
however we can eat some berries to go over that
next we had got this supposedly OP node from our quest
if that one was overpowered
then how do we call the node Berta just made
meanwhile
our dtpf hangar has been stocking up some fuel for our dtpf
it runs on excited catalysts
which take quite a while to craft
one day we will manage to craft a plasma mixer
that will do all of these steps in a single machine
and in 5 seconds instead of 700 seconds over 32 machines
however that plasma mixer is kind of expensive to craft
but fear not, Berta got our back covered
and our batteries drained
anyways the day has finally come
and we now have a working plasma mixer
but our power generation prevents us from using it
so let's work on a better generator
the power from nuclear fusion didn't last enough to make it capable of self expanding
the power of naquadah still wasn't enough for us
so we have decided that we have to take over a star
and sip all of its power to sustain ourselves
we are going to shoot giant mirrors around a star
and have them focus all of its power on our receiver tower
thus building a Dyson sphere
here you can see how much stuff goes inside the satellites
that we are going to keep shooting around the stars we will take over
we will have to keep making new ones
since sometimes they will collide
and thus get destroyed
meanwhile Berta is taking care of the receiver tower and satellite launcher
and exactly when we thought we were done
we found a better start to harvest
so we moved everything over to a new planet
and here we go
this is the full structure with its dedicated crypto farm
to help it calculate the trajectory of the satellites
so that they will crash less often
it is now outputting 138 billion EU per tick
and it is not even close to being fully loaded
this is just a test run
we also have this magic wall which blocks meteorites
but lets satellites pass
anyways guys
building this structure took longer than expected
due to some expensive parts requiring a couple of thousands of UIV motors
and during this time
many things have happened all around our base
let's see some of the less interesting
we have managed to almost fill all of our CPUs
we have crafted one UEV capacitor
these require 8 really ultimate battery
and then only difference is that they can interact with the wireless energy network 100 times faster
The Wireless Energy Network is a virtual battery
that can hold an enormous amount of power
which lapotronic supercapacitors can balance against
we also had made a fuel that was able to produce 18 billion EU/t
to help us build our Dyson Sphere
we have upgraded our carbon production using weird tricks
we have pushed the maceration stack to its limits
we have reached terawatt voltage energy tier
next we made a digital singularity cell
so that we can finally stop voiding stone dust
and I almost forgot
this is our old platline
which produces some dusts and is quite laggy
so it is time to use this handy machine
which can do the work of all of these machines alone
and can also do infinite parallels
here you can read by yourself this funny detailed description of how exactly this complex machine works
this machine is so good that we have made some more right away
we are going to use it for plastics, rubbers and other stuff
we have also increased the size of our Fusion Tower
new PCB plant
bigger radox factory
and many more things
anyways going back to the present
our Dyson Sphere center crashed 3 out of 4,000 mirrors last hour
but it produced quite a lot of power
however our power meter is no longer reliable
since it only measures the power flowing in the LSC in our base
anyways, we should keep focusing on the main quests if we want to succeed in our Stargate mission
the next quest requires us to bend reality at our own will
this means to liquefy space time
and then mold it into a solid ingot
to do so we first need to upgrade our dtpf at Hypogen tier
Today we are going to do a few upgrades to our base
like adding a few more fusion reactors
or adding some more bacterial vats
and maybe a second space elevator
we could also rebuild our ae2 controller
or have a few more alloy blast smelters
or some more generic purpose machines
and we must not forget to upgrade our dtpf
I mean not just the coils we need it to be bigger
however getting there has not been easy
we also had many mishaps during this journey
we usually don't show that part
but everyone has its own struggles
anyways, let's now see some more details of our progression
now that we have access to space time
we can make eternal singularity in a cheap way
we no longer need to mine hundreds of chunk for it
we have a machine that uses more than a Dyson sphere worth of energy
and a new laser for power transfer
now we have also unlocked crafting input buffers and slaves
which allow for machines to share crafting tasks
and here you can see why we had to go to such lengths
these are the materials in queue
for the next upgrade
we are going to need some eternal coils
which are made out of optical main frames and space time
our hypogen DTPFs require 8 hypogen ingots to make 1 space time ingot
when we will have eternal coils
it will take no hypogen to make 4 space time ingots
the other thing we are going to need for eternal coils are optical main frames
so we made a facility dedicated to its production
by the way we have started using Infinity cables
we are using the double ones
not because we need their amperage
but because we already had crafted them
and are too lazy to make a new pattern for the single wires
and the real reason why we are using these is because
now infinity is a waste byproduct
it is being made passively here
we have a dtpf dedicated to making transcendent residue
which is required for space time and Shirabon
however, working Infinity takes quite some power and time
and our machines are starting to get clogged by all of the crafting tasks
so we added even more slave machines to help the main ones finish all of these craftings
and we even had to start labeling them to remember what they are doing
however there are some which I have no idea what they have been built for
hopefully Berta will be able to help us
after making all of these machines
we have finally managed to obtain the so wanted eternal coil dtpf
however, making all these coils required a lot of optical main frames
which contain quite some holmium dust
which is currently being made by this old setup
it's so old that it still runs on EV in some parts
we could overclock it
but the best solution is to tear it down
and replace it with a quantum force transformer
however we need a tier 2 one for this recipe
which requires some plasmas that take way too long for a single fusion reactor MK4
so we are going to start working on a compact fusion reactor MK4
and it was then that we realized that this crafting is scary
I mean just look at it
it takes ages just to scroll the absurd amount of stuff that goes inside it
and I have no idea of what voice lines to add while I'm scrolling
that's probably the worst part
not to mention the power usage
and the fact that all of our new machines are clogged again
and thus new arrays of machines shall arise
some time has passed
and we now do have a compact Fusion MK4 reactor
and a tier 2 quantum force transformer
which has already made enough holmium for the rest of the year
I mean day
now that we can make more optical circuits
we can add two new layers to our optical facility
and thus unlock the last tier of Circuit
which allowed us to reach the UMV tier
now that we have UXV circuits and UMV parts
we can finally craft a deep dark portal
deep dark is a place where every mineral that can be seen on NEI spawns
and so we can move all of our void miners there
mining every existing mineral means that we are also mining holmium
which is not an issue anymore thanks to our new QFT
next we need UMV hatches to progress
these looked easy to make
until we realized that the UMV superconductor requires dragon blood to be made
the only way to make it in industrial amounts
requires a machine that needs some magical parts to be made
the process of obtaining such machine required some questionable methods
like doing weird farms
laggy and buggy farms
which I should have not come close by
we had to make weird altars
and weird rituals
that ended up creating a new civilization on otherwise dead planets
and after defeating pixelated bosses
we have finally obtained the machinery that will produce the so wanted dragon blood
meanwhile we have also made a few more DTFPs
but they were still too slow
even though they are eating half a Dyson sphere worth of power
but before making more
we had to take a look at the fuel production
adding more fusion reactor did not help
so we will have to work on something that will take care of it once forever
but that machine is kinda complex to make
and it does not have a quest about it
so we shall take care of it next time
and for now just move on with some more energy production
and do one more quest of the main line
we are now going to craft a Giga Chad token
we make a pattern for it
and add it to the others in our dtpf cluster
just look at how Chad that texture is when mixed with the others
and we then proceed into starting its crafting
and after some time
we have finally proved of being worthy
and so we can now waste some time and play Snapchat
and I think it is now a good time to close this episode
next time we will be working on eye of harmony
bye bye
上一期我们通过添加大型无限涡轮机解决了能源问题
但我们也发现：这只是把问题
从电池转移到了镅等离子体储罐
为了解决这个新问题
我们着手提升镅等离子体产量
造了个稍大点的聚变反应堆
也叫紧凑型反应堆
现在你可以助手正在建造它
每次大约100个方块
现在反应堆能跟上涡轮机需求了
新问题来了
我们生产的镅等离子体太多了
冷却速度跟不上
于是我们造了台巨型真空冷冻机
但这玩意太耗电了
所以我们转而造了更多涡轮机
接着我们发现钚正在被疯狂消耗
于是在织女星B增加了更多虚空矿机
但这导致鿫耗尽了
旧产线跟不上新需求
于是我们建了更大的生产工厂
旧高炉处理不了如此多材料
我们不得不升级冶炼设施
结果又回到了最初的问题
而这问题在开始造这些东西前根本不存在
再次解决生产问题前
我们得先修复能源输送问题
旧激光只能传输20亿EU/t
所以我们用更高级的线路替换主干线
现在能承载320亿了
忙完这些后
我们发现无限涡轮机并非无限
它们的耐久快掉光了
好吧，在对着屏幕瞪眼很久之后
我们终于明确了下一步计划
明白除了"为了录下来做视频
而做两遍一样的事"以外的事
结论很简单
该继续推进主线任务了
于是我们做了些光学电路
以及新等级的聚变反应堆
用来制造海珀珍
又一个关键材料
但有个难点：制造它需要些恶心材料
比如龙血
我们很早前通过击杀末影龙获得过龙血
在海珀珍制造的同时
我们发现固化它需要大量能源
必须升级机器了
你根本想不到我们重复过多少次这流程了
我们又发现制造一块海珀珍锭要半小时
由于这个原因
我们手动冷却了唯一的锭
以便继续推进任务
你可以看到神明是如何诱惑我们的
但我们已通关传送门
知道那蛋糕是个谎言
不能上当，必须继续前进
于是我们开始研制海珀珍线圈
但我们现在连无尽线圈都造不起
在等待无尽生产时
我们检查新队友建造的发电厂
燃料在这反应堆里燃烧产生巨量能源
看这些数据就知道
这是我们的新总产能
总之
我们总算凑够了任务所需的线圈
从而解锁了海珀珍线圈
如任务书所说
这材料相当奇特
用它制成的线圈每个方块都需要主机
但在制造前
我们必须先研究它们
于是遇到了新问题
量子计算机算力不够了
我们需要更好的
我们建了新机房容纳所有新电脑
开始安装GPU和大量散热片
我们甚至为此订购了新批次GPU
现在是时候启动它们了
并检查是否运行正常
一番测试和调试后
发现有一台没装GPU
解决所有问题后
终于可以开始研究海珀珍线圈了
凭借每秒3.2亿亿次浮点运算的算力
现在我们解锁了配方
我们发现根本造不起它
太缺龙血了
虽然可以用复杂流程再生产些
但或许该试试其他途径
换个任务试试
比如那个
但在制造更多电池前
我们得先降低成本
但这需要更多无尽催化剂
所以我们在新行星增加些虚空矿机
在收集材料时
我们顺便整理一下AE系统
将过满存储元件的内容移至量子箱
我们还需储备更多不稳定粉尘
有了新机器
我们可以更低成本地制造部件
让我们回到主线
电池任务已完成
下一个任务看起来不难
只需制造四个方块
让我看看怎么制造
应该能搞定
材料基本都有
而且也可以研究它
开工吧
但我们得先升级发电
我们升级了硅岩发电
现在能达到每tick 50亿EU
我们硅岩产线已经直冲云霄
机器消耗已超过产量
又开采了几个行星后
终于能制造完成下个任务所需的最后部件
也就是制造"超维度等离子锻炉"
简称DTPF
开始吧
这个多方块结构很大
要完成后续任务
至少需要无尽线圈
我们从而解锁了转转和转转粉
而它们用途广泛
上次以来发生了很多事
但我们先说最没用的
刚才发现我们填满了一个经验方尖碑
它能提供的等级上限是3125级
但吃经验浆果能突破这个限制
任务给了这个号称超模的节点
如果这就算超模
那Berta刚造的节点算什么
我们储备了不少DTPF需要的燃料
它消耗激发的催化剂
制作耗时很长
总有一天我们会造出蓝搅拌
一步完成所有流程
只需5秒，而不是32台机器共计700秒
但蓝搅拌造价昂贵
别担心，Berta会帮我们
电池又耗尽了
这一天终于到来
现在有了可用的蓝搅拌
但发电量跟不上使用需求
得造更好的发电机
核聚变的能源不够支撑它自我扩张
硅岩发电也不够用
我们决定占领一颗恒星
吸干它的能量供养我们
我们要在恒星周围发射巨型镜面
将能量聚焦到接收塔
也就是戴森球
看一下造个卫星需要多少材料
我们将不断发射卫星到我们占领的恒星附近
需要持续制造新的模块
因为它们有时会碰撞
然后损毁
同时Berta在负责接收塔和卫星发射器
就在我们刚以为完成时
我们发现了更好的目标恒星
所以把一切搬到了新行星
搞定
这是完整结构及其专用算力
帮助计算卫星轨道
减少碰撞频率
当前输出每tick 1380亿EU
它远未满载
这只是试运行
还有这面能阻挡陨石但可以让卫星通过的魔法墙
总之各位
建造这机器比预期的久
因为某些昂贵部件需要数千个UIV马达
在这段时间里
基地发生了很多事
挑些不太有趣的说
CPU几乎全占满了
我们造了一个UEV电容
它需要8个究极终极电池
区别是与无线电网的上下行速度快100倍
无线电网是一块虚拟电池
能储存巨量能源
而兰波顿电容库（LSC）
可以和它互相平衡电量
我们还制造了能产生180亿EU/t的燃料
来帮助我们建造戴森球
我们用特殊技巧升级了碳产量
我们把粉碎机的功率堆到了极限
达到了太瓦级电压
造了数字奇点存储元件
终于不用再销毁石头粉了
差点忘了
这是旧的铂产线
生产矿粉却很卡顿
是时候用这台便利机器了
能单独完成所有这些机器的工作
还能无限并行
你可自行阅读这台复杂机器的详细说明
这机器太棒了，所以赶紧再来几台
用于塑料、橡胶等材料生产
我们还扩大了聚变塔规模
新PCB工厂
更大的拉多X工厂
以及其他许多设施
回到现在
戴森球中心上一小时撞毁了4000面镜子中的3面
但产能巨大
我们的电表已不可靠
因为它只测量基地LSC的电量
总之，想完成星门任务还得聚焦主线
下个任务要求我们随意扭曲现实
意味着液化时空
然后铸造成固态锭
为此，我们先将DTPF升级至海珀珍线圈
今天我们要给基地做些升级
比如增加几个聚变堆
或添些细菌培养罐
或许再造个太空电梯
还可以重建AE控制器
或增加几台合金炉
以及一些通用机器
别忘了升级DTPF
不仅是线圈，还要扩大规模
但实现过程并不轻松
旅途中有不少波折
我们通常不展示那些部分
但每个人都有自己的难处
不论如何，让我们看看进展如何
拥有时空材料后
我们可用廉价方式制造永恒奇点
无需再开采数百区块
这台机器消耗相当于整个戴森球的能量
还有新的激光传电
现在我们解锁了样板输入总成和镜像
让机器能共享合成任务
这就是为何要做到这种程度
这些是排队中的材料
关于下次升级
我们需要些永恒线圈
由光学主机和时空材料制成
海珀珍DTPF需要8个海珀珍锭来造1个时空锭
有了永恒线圈后
无需海珀珍就能造4个时空锭
永恒线圈还需要光学主机
我们建了专门的生产设施
顺便开始使用无尽线缆
用的是2x款
不是需要其载流量
而是只因为它已经写好样板了
我们懒得为1x线再写样板
用它的真正原因是
现在无尽材料是副产品废料
在这里被动生产
有台DTPF专门制造转转
这是时空和调律源金的必需品
但处理无尽材料相当耗电耗时
机器开始被合成任务堵塞
所以我们增加了更多从机帮助主机完成任务
甚至开始贴标签记录用途
但有些机器根本不知道造来干嘛
希望Berta能帮忙
造完这些机器后
我们终于得到了梦寐以求的永恒线圈DTPF
但制造这些线圈需要大量光学主机
这需要不少钬粉
钬粉目前由这套旧设备生产
老旧到部分机器仍以EV电压运行
我们可以给它超频
但最好拆掉重建
换成量子操控者（QFT）
但这配方需要二级量操
所需等离子体靠单台MK4聚变堆耗时太长
所以我们开始研制压缩聚变反应堆MK4
这才发现这合成很吓人
看看就知道
光滚动查看所需材料就要半天
滚动时都不知道该配什么解说
这大概是最糟的部分
更别提能耗了
而且新机器又堵塞了
又得新建机器阵列
一段时间后
现在有了压聚MK4
和二阶量子操纵者
生产的钬粉能玩一年
我是说一整天
我们现在能制造更多光学电路板
给光学设施增加两个新层
从而解锁最终阶电路板
允许我们进入UMV电压
有了UXV电路和UMV部件
我们终于能去DD了
深暗之地生成NEI显示的所有矿物
我们可将所有虚空矿机迁往那里
开采所有矿物意味着也采集钬
有了新QFT这已不是问题
我们需要UMV能源仓来推主线
这看起来容易制造
直到我们发现UMV超导体需要龙血
工业量产它的唯一方法
需要含魔法部件的机器
获取过程用了以一些可疑手段
比如建造个奇特农场
卡顿又出错的农场
我不该靠近这里
我们建造了奇怪祭坛
进行诡异的仪式
在死寂行星上催生了新文明
击败像素boss后
我们终于得到了能生产梦寐以求的龙血的机器
同时造了几个DTPF
但还是太慢
尽管它们在吃半个戴森球的电量
但在造更多的东西前
我们得检查燃料生产
增加聚变堆没用
得研制一劳永逸的解决方案
但那机器制造复杂
且没有相关任务
所以我们留到下次处理
现在先增加能源生产
再完成一个主线任务
现在制造不再是弱鸡的证明
制作样板
加入DTPF集群的其他任务中
看这贴图和其他样板摆一起时多霸气
开始制造
在一段时间后
我们终于证明了自身价值
现在可以消磨时间玩Snapchat了
现在是时候结束本集了
下期我们将研制鸿蒙之眼
拜拜